<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[The Who You Now Dev Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://blog.whoyouknow.in/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blog.whoyouknow.in/"/>
  <updated>2012-10-14T01:29:25-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://blog.whoyouknow.in/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Team PDXCubano]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Night Two - Burning the Midnight Oil]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.whoyouknow.in/blog/2012/10/14/night-two-burning-the-midnight-oil/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-14T01:20:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.whoyouknow.in/blog/2012/10/14/night-two-burning-the-midnight-oil</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://blog.whoyouknow.in/images/photo2.jpg" alt="Developers Working" /></p>

<p>Huge developer day today.  David, Nic and I pushed hard all day long, breaking only for Mexican food and coffee.  We have a styles in place, the vast majority of the backend work done and a really solid experiance. It was a huge moment when we each loaded up our LinkedIn profiles and saw that we all actually had matches with our data! It really felt good to validate the concept and see actually interesting results right off the bat.</p>

<p>Our team was finally fully assibled around 10:00 pm tonight as Matt&#8217;s flight got it and he made his way to the dev cave. The four of us have talked about when to feature freeze (1pm tomorrow) and what fancy things we&#8217;d like to add now that the basic features are all up.  Favorites, the last of the prediscussed features, is getting wrapped up right now and then it is time for some sleep.</p>

<ul>
<li>Rob</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Night One - Wow That Went Well]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.whoyouknow.in/blog/2012/10/13/night-one-wow/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-13T14:04:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.whoyouknow.in/blog/2012/10/13/night-one-wow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our goals for the tonight where to get a Rails template generated (go go gadget rails_app_composer), login with LinkedIn working and the deployment fully functioning.  I was feeling like if we could do that and still get a solid nights sleep we&#8217;d be in a really solid place to tacle the main app functionality tomorrow.  8:30 pm was way to early to go to bed and that&#8217;s when we&#8217;d met that goal.  So we grabbed some beers, double down on our goals and started parsing job feeds and LinkedIn data.  I&#8217;m feeling really great about where we are and am still looking a full night sleep tonight.  That should leave our team in a great place tomorrow.  Looking at the other entries, I&#8217;m astonded by how many don&#8217;t have project names or descriptions yet.  I would have thought more people would have done the pre work.  And I don&#8217;t see hardly any that are deployed yet.  Feels good to be out in front.</p>

<ul>
<li>Rob</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Night One - Eager to Start]]></title>
    <link href="http://blog.whoyouknow.in/blog/2012/10/13/night-one-eager-to-start/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-13T14:03:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://blog.whoyouknow.in/blog/2012/10/13/night-one-eager-to-start</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here on the Pacific coast the Rumble starts at 5 pm. I traveled up from San Diego (where it was raining) to Portland (where it is always raining) yesterday and am totally ready for the startter gun to go off.  Our team has met a few set backs already: Matt flew out this afternoon to go to a funeral and won&#8217;t be able to join us until late Saturday and we discovered last night that Nic is too allergic to Matt&#8217;s cats to do the rumble at our planned location.  But I&#8217;m still very optimistic. Our idea is sound, we&#8217;ve got a broadly experianced team and some basic wireframe ideas already in front of us. We are ready. Here we go!</p>

<ul>
<li>Rob</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
